adrevolver.com 2009-03-03

# Privacy Policy - BlueLithium

Your privacy is important, so **BlueLithium, Inc., a Yahoo! company,** has created the following Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit our web sites and when we serve advertisements on our network of websites (collectively, the "BlueLithium Network"), why we collect it and how it is used.

The terms "you," "your," and "yours" refer to the web surfer and/or consumer utilizing our Network. The terms "BlueLithium," "we," "us," and "our" refer to BlueLithium, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates. This Privacy Policy explains only the data collection and use practices on the BlueLithium Network and does not apply to any other third party online or offline sites, products or services. To learn more about Yahoo!'s use of information please read the [Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://www.yahoo.com/r/pv).

## Privacy Commitment

BlueLithium is a Yahoo! company and shares Yahoo!'s commitment to privacy. Yahoo! is a member of the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) and works with industry leading companies to address important privacy and consumer protection issues in online advertising.

## What Information Is Collected?

The BlueLithium Network contains more than 1,000 websites, including Yahoo! websites, to which we deliver advertisements and which you, the web surfer, may occasionally visit. During your visit to the BlueLithium Network, BlueLithium and/or our third party vendors may collect certain information, as follows.

##### Personally Identifiable Information

"Personally Identifiable Information" or "PII" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, home or other physical address, an email address, phone number or other contact information, whether at work or at home.

To access certain websites operated by BlueLithium in the BlueLithium Network, we may ask you to register and provide certain PII. BlueLithium is committed to making sure that you have clear notice and choice before sharing any PII and that you have opted-in to our use of such information. Web surfers who have provided PII may elect to have their data deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the requested service, by following the procedures set forth below in the "Access" section below.

##### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

BlueLithium also automatically receives and records anonymous information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website which is part of the BlueLithium Network. These server logs may include your Internet Protocol address, browser type, page you request, one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser, and responses by a web surfer to an advertisement delivered by us or our third party advertising vendor. This information may be stored on our systems for about two years.

BlueLithium also collects non-personally identifiable information about a web surfer visiting on one or more websites owned by BlueLithium or participating in the BlueLithium Network. Examples of such non-personally identifiable data include age, gender, and interests.

As a rule, non-personally identifiable information is anonymous and is not used to identify a specific person by BlueLithium.

Web surfers may elect not to provide non-personally identifiable information by following the cookie opt-out procedures set forth below.

## How Is Such Information Used?

##### Non-personally identifiable information

BlueLithium will use your non-personal information in order to better target advertisements across the BlueLithium Network, to provide aggregate reporting to advertisers and clients, and to improve our advertising systems and products. In addition, that data may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to a consumer's preferences and behaviors. We may also share non-personally identifiable information with our subsidiaries and third party partners for similar use.

##### Personally identifiable information

We collect PII from customers who are individuals or companies that wish to enter into business relationships with BlueLithium, including websites and online marketers. This customer information is used only for purposes of administering these relationships, including maintaining account information and managing payments. In addition, our lead generation business may gather personally identifiable information on behalf of our clients. In such cases, we send this information directly to our clients.

BlueLithium may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on BlueLithium; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of BlueLithium; or (3) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of BlueLithium, its websites or the public. If BlueLithium should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, we may sell the information you provide to us to a third party or share your PII with any company with whom we merge or that acquires all or substantially all of our stock or assets.

## Access

BlueLithium allows visitors to the BlueLithium Network who have provided PII to access, correct, amend or delete any information they have provided by sending us an email at the contact listed below. Customers are provided access to their account so that they can view and update their information as needed.

## Choice and Opt-Out

##### Non-personally identifiable information

BlueLithium uses technology, including technology from its third party advertising vendors, which includes cookies, "web beacons" and/or "action tags". A "cookie" is a small text file stored by your browser on your computer when you visit our Network. A "web beacon" or "action tag" is a small image (usually 1x1 pixel) embedded in a web page or email. We use cookies, web beacons and action tags to collect non-personally identifiable data to provide better and more relevant services and messages to that user. Cookies, web beacons and action tags permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information.

If you prefer not to receive behaviorally targeted ads delivered by BlueLithium we allow you to [opt-out](http://www.bluelithium.com/optout.html) of this anonymous ad targeting. Please note that if you opt-out BlueLithium will continue to collect non-personal information in connection with ad serving for limited reporting and auditing purposes. Examples of these include but are not limited to reporting overall advertising performance, geographic activity, and other similar analyses.Most browsers will accept cookies unless you change your browser settings to refuse them and opt-out of the use of BlueLithium cookies and those of our third party advertising technology vendors. For more information on cookies and how to manage and delete them, please visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

##### Personally identifiable information

When you sign up for a particular BlueLithium service that requires registration, we ask you to provide certain PII. If we use this PII in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will seek your consent prior to such use. If we propose to use PII for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. You can decline to submit PII to any of our services, in which case BlueLithium may not be able to provide those services to you.

## The Security of Your Information

BlueLithium uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to BlueLithium and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, BlueLithium makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

## International Transfers

Personal information collected on the BlueLithium websites may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which BlueLithium, Yahoo! or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this web site, you acknowledge and agree that you may be transferring your personal information outside of the country in which you live and that you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

## Children

BlueLithium's websites, products and services are not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 13. For that reason, BlueLithium does not knowingly collect or maintain PII or non-personally identifiable information on the BlueLithium websites from persons under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not use or access the BlueLithium websites at any time or in any manner. Any person who provides their information to BlueLithium through the login page for new customers or website users or any other part of the BlueLithium Network represents to BlueLithium that they are 13 years of age or older. If BlueLithium learns that PII of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the BlueLithium websites without verified parental consent, then BlueLithium will take appropriate steps to delete this information.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the Privacy Policy. For changes to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information, or notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our web site or by directly sending you a notification. For all other changes, it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often. Your continued use of the Network constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Statement and any updates.

## Contacting BlueLithium

If you have any additional questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at:

By email: [privacy@bluelithium.com](mailto:privacy@bluelithium.com)

By postal mail:  
3055 Olin Avenue  
Suite 2200  
San Jose, CA 95128

Effective Date:  
Last Updated: December 3, 2007
